Men's mental health is something that is super important to talk about and just a really
important discussion in general, but I think the way that we look at it right now and the way we
discuss it is counterproductive and honestly really really frustrating to me. I feel like a
lot of the advocacy surrounding men's mental health is centered around this idea that like
men can't cry and society doesn't accept men for having emotions. And I find this line of
reasoning a little bit frustrating just because I feel like it suggests that women are accepted by
society for being emotional and that's just not true. Just because women are more openly emotional
despite scrutiny does not mean that society and the media is like embracing it. The idea that
women are too emotional is constantly being used to put women down and like say that they're weaker
and I also think it's just super important to talk about because being emotionally vulnerable
is not easy and I feel like sometimes it's seen like women have it easier because they're allowed
to be emotional and they're allowed to cry. No, they have the strength to do it anyway despite
scrutiny and to act like it's easier for women is just really frustrating to me. Basically what I'm
saying is the big issue in terms of men's mental health stems from the fact that like men's
relationship and friendships with other men don't leave room for that like emotional connection that
exists within like female relationships and female friendship. In order to facilitate progress in
terms of men's mental health I think what needs to be looked at is what's happening within male
spaces and not necessarily from a societal really broad standpoint because
from that broader standpoint society needs to work on accepting both genders
and this definitely is not an argument to say that like men's mental health doesn't
matter and like focusing on men's mental health is sex it's not all we need to
talk about men's mental health because it's a huge problem but we're looking at it from
like the bottom down and we need to look at it from down up if that makes sense
obviously I can only speak from the perspective of a woman but I really
think it's important that we change the conversation regarding men's mental
health because it is important and it needs to be looked at correctly that's
all she wrote bye guys